<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Aaron Hong</title>
    <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/techs/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Aaron Hong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>@Aaron Hong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/techs/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exoplanets</title>
      <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/exoplanets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/exoplanets/</guid>
      <description>ML-Project-4-Exoplanets Project Goal The goal of this project was to predict potential exoplanets that are earth-sized and smaller within the habitable zone of their respective sun using a variety of classification models.
Conclusion After extracting 2418 candidates, I used my best two models to classify them.
 SVC predicted there would be 994 potential earth-sized and smaller exoplanets within the habitable zone Random Forest predicted there would be 829 potential earth-sized and smaller exoplanets within the habitable zone  If I was part of NASA&amp;rsquo;s team that is involved in the Kepler&amp;rsquo;s mission, I would attempt to validate the candidates my models predicted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/btc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/btc/</guid>
      <description>ML-Project-3-Bitcoin Project Goal The goal of this project was to predict bitcoin (btc) prices using RNN. One thing to note is that; bitcoin is known to be very manipulated so I did not expect my model to perform well.
Conclusion In this project, I&amp;rsquo;ve built two different RNN model;
  RNN without Time Series Generator
 MAE: 4391.88 RMSE: 4843.59    RNN with Time Series Generator
 MAE: 603.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar irradiance</title>
      <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/solar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/solar/</guid>
      <description>ML-Project-5-Solar-Irradiance Project Goal The goal of this project was to predict solar irradiance based on a variety of features such as; temperature, pressure, humidity, time, and wind directions.
Live demo: Solar Irradiance
Conclusion The features that are the most relevant to solar irradiance was temperature(celsius) and day of the year. The random forest regressor was determined to be the best model which produced a mean R2 of 0.868 in cross validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug sales</title>
      <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/drugs/</guid>
      <description>ML-Project-2-Drug-Sales Project Goal The goal for this project was to predict future classes of drug sales for the following:
  N02BA - Analgesics and Antipyretics, Salicylic Acid and derivatives
  N05B - Psycholeptics drugs, Anxiolytic drugs
  Conclusion There are less consumptions of N05B &amp;amp; N02BA classes of drugs over time. There I would not rely on the final models built to predict drug sales for the classes of drugs I was interested in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Titanic</title>
      <link>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/titanic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hongphumagic.github.io/Actual-Portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/titanic/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>